Glad you're out of the hospital, Luxy!
Thanks, but you didn't need to throw me a party.
Don't be so modest.
The backlash from the Over Limit has had you bedridden ever since the training camp.
You feeling better is something to celebrate.
Yes. Everyone was worried about you.
It was especially difficult on the particular ladies over there,
who were constantly fighting over who'd take care of you.
Oh, my. This looks like a fun party.
Miss Relie!
What happened at Ries Island afterwards?
Well, after getting yelled at enough for a lifetime and
paying a substantial fine, I managed to get off the hook.
That's it? Even after conducting an
unauthorized ruin expedition?
There's a big event coming up.
They're busy with that at the capital.
A big event?
Do you mean...
Spanning several days, it's the
greatest event held by our kingdom,
the Kingdom Founding Festival!
Fight for the sky
afuredasu kanjou mou tomaranai
I can't stop the overflowing emotions
mune ni idaitai bokura no gensou
The illusions we hold so dear
Just revolution
kienai aza ni obiete ite mo
Fear of the scar that won't disappear
toki ga mujou ni sugiteku dake
Won't stop the ruthless passage of time
susumeyo aru ga mama
Go forth, the way you are
Let's burst up!
ima koso kawaru toki
Now is the time for change
Let's boost up!
kakumei no kane no ne ga
The sound of the bell of revolution
doko made mo hibiite yuku
Resounds far and wide
To be the soldier
mou koko ni wa irarenai
We can't stay here any longer
To be the soldier
kaze wo kitte yuke ikite yuke
Cut through the wind, live your life
hiryuu no gotoku
Like a flying dragon
hajimari ga michiru mama densetsu ni nare
As the beginning draws near, become a legend
tokihanatte yuke tonde yuke
Release yourself, fly ahead
inochi wo tagirasete
Overflow with life
erabareshi mono wo matsu sekai wa owari da New age
The world that waits for a chosen one is over! New age!
m 448.23 457.02 b 448.23 465.7 446.7 475.77 448.23 484.27 448.74 487.11 448.87 487.03 450.28 489.07 451.18 490.38 454.48 489.87 451.7 491.62 450.4 492.44 437.17 492.56 436.11 491.62 433.39 489.2 439.08 489.4 439.68 488.47 440.65 486.98 440.26 485.18 440.38 483.51 440.74 478.44 440.38 473.22 440.38 468.14 440.38 465.92 441.4 458.27 439.89 457.02 434.19 452.32 433.28 464.87 428.93 463.57 429.23 461.29 429.02 455.14 430.59 454.02 432.79 452.46 441.65 454.02 444.3 454.02 446.86 454.02 455.62 452.53 457.77 454.02 459.52 455.24 459.31 461.03 459.63 463.57 455.42 464.69 457.23 461.21 455.43 458.92 453.59 456.58 451.2 456.92 448.23 457.02 m 461.68 489.47 b 466.42 489.47 466.37 463.12 464.63 458.7 463.35 455.44 459.16 457.17 463.84 454.54 465.55 453.58 470.94 451.84 472.08 453.2 473.92 455.41 472.08 466.61 472.08 469.67 478.84 463.11 487.22 464.65 488.13 474.4 488.53 478.75 487.12 483.89 488.38 488.1 488.87 489.76 492.12 489.55 490.38 491.62 489.84 492.27 483.58 491.72 482.73 491.62 475.79 490.87 480.01 490.65 480.78 484.97 481.15 482.25 481.99 471.79 479.78 469.75 472.8 463.31 472.06 478.05 472.08 480.98 472.09 483.83 474.16 491.47 474.02 491.62 472.75 493.07 460.96 492.85 461.68 489.47 m 516.93 485.97 b 508.89 500.58 489.16 488.48 494.05 473.65 498.67 459.67 517.08 465.2 517.08 478.87 511.78 478.87 506.48 478.87 501.18 478.87 501.18 483.26 502.26 489.25 507.73 489.57 512.23 489.84 513.44 483.69 516.93 485.97 m 509.58 476.57 b 509.58 466.06 501.18 466.1 501.18 476.57 503.98 476.57 506.78 476.57 509.58 476.57 m 557.58 464.97 b 554.93 449.47 543.02 458.15 542.11 469.66 541.71 474.8 541.81 482.43 545.39 486.58 547.71 489.27 552.54 490.89 554.58 487.13 557.32 482.06 550.2 477.32 552.08 476.02 553.04 475.36 561.06 475.67 562.1 476.02 563.39 476.46 563.66 475.51 564.18 476.62 565.25 478.94 562.46 478.03 562.35 478.66 561.33 484.4 562.79 488.64 555.82 491.22 545.43 495.08 536.14 488.86 534.22 478.33 532.47 468.75 535.42 457.08 545.76 454.01 549.94 452.77 557.22 452.71 559.54 456.26 561.35 459.02 561.89 465.4 557.58 464.97 m 577.48 465.97 b 577.48 471.84 576.08 479.71 577.48 485.38 578.03 487.63 580.73 490.95 580.11 491.62 579.27 492.52 570.33 491.87 569.35 491.62 568 491.29 567.36 492.17 566.88 491.09 565.71 488.44 569.02 490.21 569.6 488.8 570.73 486.06 570.08 481.6 570.08 478.68 570.08 475.38 569.09 472.5 568.63 470.07 567.13 470.57 566.54 470.2 566.88 468.97 566.55 467.29 567.6 466.82 570.03 467.57 571.98 466.52 575.6 465.96 577.48 465.97 m 573.48 454.27 b 578.99 454.27 578.95 463.05 573.48 463.02 568.05 463 568.04 454.27 573.48 454.27 m 593.13 469.67 b 595.85 465.93 607.42 463.93 604.05 471.25 601.43 476.94 597.09 463.67 593.28 473.04 592.29 475.46 592.6 482.76 593.28 485.38 594.58 490.45 599.4 490.2 593.39 491.62 590.33 492.35 583.52 492.66 582.93 490.01 583.43 492.27 585.89 485.54 585.93 485.38 586.41 483.33 585.93 480.67 585.93 478.58 585.93 476.99 586.49 474.23 585.89 472.72 585.36 471.39 582.87 469.37 582.93 468.97 583.08 467.85 594.6 461.74 593.13 469.67 m 606.33 489.47 b 612.18 489.47 609.81 466.82 609.58 462.36 609.5 460.97 609.78 459.48 609.29 458.16 608.45 455.89 604.19 457.35 607.43 454.72 607.97 454.29 616.04 452.27 616.71 452.77 617.35 453.25 616.73 454.96 616.93 455.68 619.39 464.88 614.6 475.98 616.93 485.23 618.02 489.55 621.86 490.44 617.4 491.62 614.73 492.33 605.69 493.1 606.33 489.47 m 624.53 483.57 b 625.48 487.01 630.81 493.5 634.45 488.48 638.15 483.37 628.35 480.37 625.9 477.77 621.35 472.94 622.86 468.01 629.08 466.04 631.24 465.36 635.41 464.9 637.6 465.87 641.64 467.67 640.69 468.56 641.58 472.77 638.3 474.12 636.52 464.03 631.4 468.52 626.51 472.82 639.67 477.49 641.48 480.46 645.58 487.19 639.42 491.62 633.22 492.19 631.05 492.39 626.13 492.59 624.28 491.08 622.62 489.72 620.85 483.77 624.53 483.57 m 646.92 465.37 b 648.71 464.03 650.36 462.01 650.47 459.67 646.19 463.96 643.41 450.29 651.22 453.61 656.84 456 650.76 469.59 646.92 465.37 m 684.82 454.02 b 690.61 454.02 697.52 455.19 699.27 461.6 700.8 467.17 696.88 472.53 691.52 473.77 694.39 478.93 698.95 484.33 701.45 489.12 703.02 492.12 702.18 491.62 697.72 491.62 693.53 491.62 694.23 491.92 691.94 489.88 690.03 488.17 685.47 472.02 681.82 474.82 681.08 475.4 681.67 482.84 681.82 483.92 682.05 485.48 681.64 487.01 682.37 488.52 683.28 490.41 686.03 487.79 685.37 491.02 685.17 492.01 669.83 492.87 669.87 490.42 669.91 488.55 672.59 489.22 673.8 487.12 674.22 486.38 673.79 485 673.92 484.13 674.42 480.88 673.92 477.05 673.92 473.77 673.92 470.01 674.17 466.14 673.92 462.39 673.89 461.91 674.03 461.26 673.92 460.77 674.1 459.5 673.88 458.32 673.27 457.22 672.26 456.52 671.13 456.27 669.87 456.47 668.47 451.99 681.88 454.02 684.82 454.02 m 683.12 456.92 b 680.78 456.92 681.51 471.24 682.4 471.92 689.16 477.11 697.98 454.92 683.12 456.92 m 728.12 485.97 b 720.08 500.58 700.35 488.48 705.25 473.65 709.86 459.67 728.27 465.2 728.27 478.87 722.97 478.87 717.67 478.87 712.37 478.87 712.37 483.26 713.46 489.25 718.92 489.57 723.43 489.84 724.64 483.69 728.12 485.97 m 720.77 476.57 b 720.77 466.06 712.37 466.1 712.37 476.57 715.17 476.57 717.97 476.57 720.77 476.57 m 769.32 468.32 b 763.55 468.32 764.01 489.46 760.2 492.23 754.06 496.71 751.42 477.96 750.42 474.62 748.82 478.58 747.55 490.61 744.1 492.32 737.83 495.45 735.15 476.95 733.55 473.1 732.9 471.53 729.47 466.89 730.07 466.17 730.52 465.64 741.18 465.87 741.43 466.17 742.94 468.06 739.89 468.2 739.91 468.97 739.95 470.75 740.43 472.04 740.88 473.81 741.77 477.29 742.97 481.43 744.42 484.52 745.52 480.89 749.26 474.01 748.69 470.35 748.51 469.24 746.3 467.68 746.27 467.79 746.89 465.09 747.93 466.44 750.9 466.17 759.34 465.41 755.97 466.61 755.77 471.38 755.61 475.05 758.49 481.26 759.82 484.52 761.04 480.39 764.37 474.2 764.07 469.92 763.92 467.77 760.31 467.77 763.41 466.17 765.87 464.9 769.64 465.66 769.32 468.32 m 786.62 472.97 b 786.62 469.5 784.71 466.87 781.07 468.22 778.53 469.16 779.17 472.77 776.43 473.41 771.99 474.46 772.34 470.01 774.7 467.72 777.28 465.22 783.9 465.03 787.05 465.75 793.39 467.2 793.85 471.77 793.97 477.43 794.01 479.14 792.8 491.64 796.97 489.07 798.35 496.78 788.1 489.11 786.97 489.17 782.42 489.42 779.64 495.48 773.9 490.65 761.54 480.25 787.65 477.28 786.62 472.97 m 786.62 477.42 b 783.43 478.42 779.08 480.37 779.17 484.37 779.26 487.85 782.76 490.49 785.8 487.41 787.72 485.46 786.62 480.18 786.62 477.42 m 809.52 469.67 b 812.25 465.93 823.81 463.93 820.45 471.25 817.83 476.94 813.49 463.67 809.67 473.04 808.69 475.46 809 482.76 809.67 485.38 810.97 490.45 815.79 490.2 809.79 491.62 806.73 492.35 799.91 492.66 799.32 490.01 799.83 492.27 802.29 485.54 802.32 485.38 802.8 483.33 802.32 480.67 802.32 478.58 802.32 476.99 802.89 474.23 802.28 472.72 801.76 471.39 799.27 469.37 799.32 468.97 799.48 467.85 811 461.74 809.52 469.67 m 840.22 467.87 b 840.22 465.04 840.93 460.94 839.95 458.24 839.26 456.35 836.76 457.89 837.07 455.87 837.29 454.51 842.51 453.42 844.31 453.36 849.09 453.19 846.16 451.67 847.57 454.98 848.64 457.49 847.57 463.01 847.57 465.63 847.57 471.65 845.96 480.06 847.57 485.83 848.02 487.43 850.49 490.77 850.12 491.47 849.6 492.47 839.56 494.31 840.37 489.27 832.47 498.16 823.05 487.16 823.12 478.62 823.19 470.53 832.35 459.98 840.22 467.87 m 840.22 471.22 b 830.7 455.61 826.11 497.16 838.47 488.45 842.37 485.7 840.22 475.41 840.22 471.22
The Kingdom Founding Festival...
It's been five years since
this kingdom was founded.
Miss Lisha?
Uh... Well, um...
About the festival...
Lux, do you want to go on
a date with me at the festival?
Hold it right there!
Our captain also wanted to use this opportunity
to get to know our new member, Lux, a bit better.
H-Huh?!
What are you saying?!
I want to go on a date too, then.
Phi!
H-Hold on, all of you!
Lux will be going to the festival with me!
Jeez, everyone... Why are you all on edge all of a sudden?
How cruel of you not to grasp the situation.
All right, then,
how about we have Lux select three girls he thinks
did particularly well at the training camp,
and take them on dates as a reward?
How does that make sense?!
It'll stir things up a bit.
If they know it could lead to such opportunities, the girls will try even harder to do well.
B-But...
Hurry up and make your picks.
Everyone's waiting.
Come on, Lux!
Who are you going to pick?!
Uh...
A-All right, then...
Um...
We passed by several nobles going towards the academy. What's that about?
Oh, right, you wouldn't know.
The All Dragons Battle will be held during the festival.
That's what the nobles are here for.
All Dragons Battle?
The Machine Dragon combat tournament
where representatives of all kingdoms compete for ruins exploration rights.
And by the way, our knight squadron,
you included, will be representing our kingdom.
What?!
Really?!
But although you may be back on your feet,
you're still not ready for combat.
I'd prefer that you don't strain yourself just yet.
Also, I have to warn you about something.
I heard that the Empire's Dagger,
who was imprisoned in the capital, has escaped.
The Empire's Dagger?
Wasn't that...
The strongest Drag-Knight employed by
the imperial family of the former empire.
The report said she's coming after you,
the one who felled the empire.
Please be very careful.
Don't get yourself killed after
getting too carried away dating.
Huh?
Over here!
Wh-What do you think, Lux?
U-Um... I...
That's our Celes!
Lux is just smitten by your looks!
Why did I have to change as well?
Yes. It suits you well.
Well, you see, I thought it would set a bad example
for the captain of the squadron to do leisurely activities right before the All Dragons Battle.
If you dress up, the students
won't recognize you.
You two will look like a young noble lady and her butler.
Don't we look even more
conspicuous in these clothes?
But with this, I'll be able to experience the festival for the first time.
N-No! I'm not excited about this at all!
All right.
Let's go, milady.
I'm still dizzy.
To drink alcohol by mistake like that,
I guess even you can be careless sometimes.
Still, I'm happy I was able to see the festival.
You're amazing.
Huh?
You're the only boy in the whole school,
but everyone likes being around you.
Unlike me, who most of the students fear and avoid.
That's not true.
I have to rely on everyone for so much.
But I can't fall behind!
If you're fighting for your ideals,
I, too, have to make an effort to reach mine.
Celes...
I'll continue to pursue the path of being an exemplary Drag-Knight for you!
Of course. I'm counting on you.
Celes?
Ouch.
Are you all right, Celes?
Yes. I'm fine, but... your hands...
My hands?
Well, Luxy is one healthy young man, isn't he?
Wh-What are you doing here?!
It's almost time for your next date.
Sorry to interrupt, Celes.
You'll have to continue some other time.
My face feels even warmer now.
Is it because of the alcohol?
They made me change again.
Luxy, Luxy! There's no time to waste!
Your next date is this way.
Why are you three managing me?
What's this?
It's a social event for the nobles and Drag-Knights
gathered for the All Dragons Battle.
Oh?
Good afternoon, Lux.
May I have this dance?
Sorry. I don't really go to
these kinds of parties much.
It's a simple dance.
Just try to follow my lead.
What do you think about my dress?
Oh, um...
You look very good in it.
I thought you were a princess.
That's high praise coming from an actual prince.
Your awkward steps were quite amusing.
Don't laugh at me!
I did my best!
I'm sorry. Thank you.
To be honest, Alterize is here for the festival.
She's probably watching us
from somewhere as we speak.
Huh?!
Since when?
Don't worry about it.
I think we put up a good show for her today.
Yeah, you're right.
But it's still not enough to completely convince her.
So would you kiss me this time?
What?! Here?!
Please.
You can just pretend to kiss me, if you'd prefer.
A-All right...
That was the first time you were the initiator.
It feels quite different.
All right, I'll go talk to Alterize. Bye.
K-Krulcifer is as mature as ever.
You have a formidable opponent, Celes.
It's almost time for the last date.
Sorry I'm late, Phi!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
Um... You look good in that dress.
Th-Thank you.
Finally, the last date.
Yes. We don't need to escort him any more.
This is your time to shine, Phi!
Headmistress?!
Why are you here?!
Are you sure this is where you want to go?
Yeah. Have a seat.
Are you hungry? Should I go get something?
No. Come here.
You should take a rest.
I can tell you're tired.
No, I'm not.
You worked hard today again.
So you have to rest.
All right, I'll take you up on that.
You can go to sleep.
I'll wake you up later.
Okay.
Thanks.
It made me happy.
When you took the blame for me in court back then.
And what you did on Ries Island.
I did want someone to help me.
I pretended I was fine, but you could always see through me.
Thank you. For finding me.
Now kiss him, Phi!
Philuffy's going to be angry
if she sees you, Headmistress.
That was a good rest.
I have to thank Phi somehow.
You're coming home late, Lux.
Miss Lisha?
For goodness sake...
Why didn't you choose me?
S-Sorry. I, um...
I get it.
I know that those three did well at the training camp.
I just had to vent.
Forget about it.
All right.
More importantly,
I've been meaning to make a personal request to you.
What is it?
Well...
W-Will you...
be my knight?
After graduation, I'll have
a more official business.
People have been telling me I should
get a personal attendant.
You're strong, you know my secret,
and most importantly...
But...
I'm a survivor of the former empire. A criminal.
I couldn't possibly...
I understand what you're saying,
and what difficulties I'd be facing.
But I'd still like you to think about it.
That's all I ask.
On the last day of the festival,
I'll be giving a speech to the people.
I'd like to introduce you
as my personal attendant then.
So give me an answer before then.
Do I really have the right to?
So you're taking part in training sessions starting today?
Yes.
I have to get back in shape for the All Dragons Battle.
But you're still taking on handyman jobs.
You're pushing yourself too hard.
I'm sorry.
Twelve minutes.
Huh?
That's how long you can ride Bahamut for right now.
You can probably go a bit longer in a Wyvern.
That short?!
In truth, it's so bad, it'd be best if you
withdrew from the tournament altogether.
You have a lot of other things you need to worry about!
Or have you forgotten?
I haven't.
Hayes and Fugil.
And the Empire's Dagger.
You called?
At last we meet, Prince Lux Arcadia.
Could she really be the Empire's Dagger?!
Run away, Lux!
You can't fight her now!
I've been looking forward to meeting you, Master.
Huh?!
My name is Kirihime Yoruka.
I'm a Drag-Knight who used
to serve the imperial family.
Have you come to kill me?
Perish the thought.
I came here with the honest desire to serve you, master.
To grant your desires.
To be tool at your beck and call.
My only wish is that you use me till my blood runs cold and my body decays.
M-Miss Yoruka...
Please, just call me Yoruka.
I'm your servant, and also a year younger.
So do you have orders for me?
O-Orders?
Assassinations. Chores.
You can use me any way you want.
A-Any way?
Lux!
Stay focused!
N-No, I wasn't looking anywhere!
Please, Master, give me my first order.
No. Let's talk again later.
I'd like you to wait until I have more time.
If those are your orders, I shall comply.
Excuse me.
Please don't let your guard down.
Okay.
But look, she's doing what I told her.
I guess I'll have her wait until the All Dragons Battle is over.
That was naive of me!
Wh-Why are you in here, Yoruka?
I thought I'd wash your back, master.
You don't need to show restraint.
I know how to treat a man after his long day's work.
Stop!
What's wrong?!
What happened?!
What? What?
Yes.
Lux...
You're the worst.
In the bath house again!
It's not what it looks like!
What do you wish to speak about?
Would you like to continue what we started in the bath house?
Not at all.
Do you know how hard it was
to calm them down afterwards?
You only had to say the word,
and they'd have never bothered you again.
Yoruka.
Why are you so devoted to serving me?
I looked into your past.
You were once a Drag-Knight from a kingdom
that the former empire conquered.
Then you made a pact with my father and joined the imperial army, right?
That's right.
To put it simply, that's my story.
But my father is dead.
You don't need to adhere to that pact.
I gave my everything to the empire.
As long as any piece of it remains,
I intend to fight.
May I also ask a question?
How long do you intend on deceiving those girls?
Wh-What do you mean?
Exactly what I said.
With your power, you can destroy this kingdom and reconstitute the empire.
You're joking, right?
Of course, I don't mind you playing the long game.
But can you swear to me here and now?
That you'll eventually destroy this kingdom
and restore the Arcadia Empire?
I'm sorry, but I have no such plans.
Are you serious about that?
Wind is coming.
Celes?!
Stand back!
She's dangerous!
Summoning without a chant?
You're pretty good, I guess.
Then I'll join you.
Allow me to introduce to you, Master, my Machine Dragon, Yato-no-kami.
So you have a Divine Raiment Machine Dragon too.
Lux!
Excuse us for ganging up on you,
but we won't hold back.
Don't be mean to Lu.
Good grief.
Caught you.
Hey! What was that, you klutz?!
Are you trying to shoot down your allies?!
Huh?
Why is my Legion doing that?!
Be careful!
It seems she can control other Machine Dragons!
Well, let's leave it at that for tonight.
Master, we shall speak about this matter again.
Are you serious about that?
My loyalty won't waver.
As proof, if you come with me,
I'll tell you a very special secret.
About a certain project which may decide this kingdom's fate.
What project?
I'm looking forward to our next meeting, Master.
It can camouflage too?
She'll be hard to deal with.
Yoruka...
What are you trying to do?
kusaki mo nemuru yoru no sumi de sekai no fushi de
In the nook of night where even trees sleep, in a cranny of the world
neiki ni sotto mimi wo tatete hitomi wo tojiru
I hear the breath of someone asleep nearby,
close my eyes, and prick up my ears
kubisuji ni futto atatakana inochi no tsubu ga
A warm seed of life near my neck
koko ni iru tte sakenderun da koe naki koe de
is screaming that it's there, in a voice without voice
umarekawaretara owarinaki you ni
If we can be reborn endlessly
kimi ga nodo wo itamenakute
Let's take such forms
sumu you na sugata ni narou
that we won't need to scream so hard to be heard
sashiatatte futari tabi doko made arukeru
Now we're traveling, the two of us. How far can we go?
ikeru toko made ikou hohaba awasete
Let's go as far as we can, matching each other's pace
tsukiatatte futari tabi koko made kureba
And when we finally get to the end of the path, the two of us
kigi ni natte tachitsukusou
Let's become trees and stay there
raise ni natte mo zutto koko de nemurou
Even in the next world, let's keep sleeping there
futari nemurou towa ni
The two of us, let's sleep for eternity
Do you really think the girl is
going to do what we expected?
She will.
That's why I freed her from the dungeon.
Everything's been set in motion.
Now it's time to go destroy this kingdom built on lies.